Eldrie?
I know that name.
Hey, get ready.
I'm gonna keep him busy.
When I give the signal, you're up. Got it.
Using your chains as a weapon, huh?
Then I'll forego my sword.
And use this instead.
System Call.
Enhance Armament.
Don't sweat it.
A whip can only reach so far.
We're safe here.
Impressive.
My divine frost scale whip is fast, but
it seems you're faster. You all right?
His whip did that?
Yu-Gi-Oh, I'll try to find
a way to stop his whip.
You sneak around back.
If you've finished plotting,
we should wrap this up.
Now, come at me and keep me entertained.
To you, the big yourself
Shining Sun My Diamond
The future of the world will be the
best you will be the best you will be.
Thermal element.
Generate cryogenic element.
Form element.
Arrow shape.
Bird shape.
Counter thermal object.
Discharge.
It seems I overestimated you.
However, I am merciful.
You'll be unconscious before you know it.
My turn!
Perhaps it was presumptuous of
me to underestimate you earlier.
It seems you've managed to
do me some harm after all.
Yeah, well, that's what you get.
I must say, your style of combat.
There's something oddly
familiar about it. Really?
Then I guess you must have come up against
a swordsman of the surloop style before.
That, my dear criminal, is not possible.
As I previously said, I was summoned as
a knight to this realm one month ago.
Yeah, right, I bet you were.
How's that work?
Does someone snap their
fingers and you come running?
Release Recollection.
No wonder Lady Alice was wary of you.
Your attacks have no pattern, which
is surprising and slightly irritating.
What irritates me more is you forced
me to use my memory release skill.
That's it.
Yeah, now I know where I
heard your name before.
You were the champion swordsman
this year for Norlinggarth Empire.
And then, you won the
unification tournament.
You're Eldriei Wolfsburg.
Champion from the Norlinggarth Empire?
Eldriei Wolfsburg?
It's true, Sir Knight.
This year, if I remember correctly, you
won every match with a single stroke.
What are you saying?
That's preposterous.
I am Eldrie Synthesis 31.
I have never heard the name
Wolfsburg before. But... Enough!
Hold your tongue, you blasphemer.
I was summoned to this
world by the Pontifex.
I am here by Administrator's will.
I descended as an Integrity Knight
from the heavens, I tell you.
What's that?
I bet Alice got one of those too when
they blocked her memory and changed her.
Eldrie!
Eldrie Wolfsburg!
Yu-Gi-Oh! Yu-Gi-Oh!
Know anything else about him?
Anything at all?
Something to trigger more of his memory?
Eldrie!
Your father is Estor Wolfsburg,
the Imperial Knight's general.
Your mother's name is, I think, Almera?
Yeah, it's Almera!
Almera...
Ma...
Thur...
That's right!
Remember her!
Kirito!
You okay?
Step away from Knight 31, criminals.
Tempting an integrity knight to
fall from grace is unforgivable.
You wretches.
I shall pin you down, then
return you to your cell.
This way!
Which way?
Go right.
Yu-Gi-Oh, go right!
Dead end up ahead!
What do we do?
Hey!
Over here!
Follow her.
Where are we?
Now they know we're here.
We can't use this back door anymore.
Thank you.
We were really in a bind.
Who are you? I'm Yu-Gi-Oh.
It's nice to meet you.
Wait a sec.
And this is Kirito.
We really appreciate your help.
Is this some...
where you live?
No, of course it isn't.
Come with me.
So, uh, are we in the Central Cathedral?
Yes and no, but neither
of you have to worry.
Although the space is
technically in the Cathedral,
I've deleted the regular doorway to it.
No one can enter here from that point now.
Well, unless I invite them.
It's a library indeed.
The records of this world's
entire history are here,
as well as the formulas of
everything created under the heavens.
That includes every system command or
what you refer to as the sacred arts.
Wait.
System commands.
Who are you?
My name is Cardinal.
I was once the regulator of this world,
but now I am the sole curator
of this great library.
All our history.
Precisely.
There is also a record of the
creation when Vecta and Stacia
split the world into the human
empire and the dark territory.
You may read them if you wish.
But first, would you hold out your
right hands?
There.
You
feeling
okay? Yeah.
You're going to catch a cold if
you stay in those wet clothes.
At the end of the hall, through
there, you'll find a small bath.
You may use.
Thanks a lot.
I'm grateful for your hospitality.
Can I um see the um record of creation?
It is located up the stairs
in the history section.
After you bathe, you may
read it. With your supper.
You're much too kind.
I'll be back in a bit. Then.
What those records won't reveal?
Is that the Pontifex of the Axiom
Church fabricated all of it?
Let me get this straight.
You're saying the gods here are fake? Yes.
The myths the people of the underworld
believe are just propaganda!
All invented by the church
to maintain its control.
The gods' names are registered as
supervisor accounts, in case of emergency.
But the humans outside
never logged in using them.
Wait a sec!
How would you know anything
about the real world?
You weren't born here, were you?
You're an outsider, just
like the system admins!
Yes.
And I know you're an outsider
too, Kirito the Unregistered.
Yeah, I am.
A company called Wrath is
the one that made this world.
You know that. Yes, I do.
Then you must be the Cardinal System.
You're an autonomous program, aren't you?
You run this world.
Ah, so you know about me.
Then you've interacted with my
kind before in the Outer World.
Oh, yeah.
But you're different.
As far as I know, the Cardinal System
never had a human-like interface.
So what kind of program are you?
What do you do here?
I'll try to be as succinct as possible.
But first, eat.
I've cast a spell on it that will
help your wounds heal faster.
Wow, now that's an admin for you.
I am not an administrator.
I can only manipulate the objects
that are contained in this library.
Oh, Cardinal, can you get in touch
with someone in the real world for me?
Of course not.
If I could do that,
I wouldn't be stuck here in this
dusty place for all these centuries.
Unfortunately, the only one who
has that authority is the Pontifex.
Ugh, crap.
There.
I told you earlier that no
gods exist in this world.
Technically that's true, but there was
once a time when something similar did.
That was about 450 years ago.
Back when Senator was no
more than a tiny village,
there were four gods.
Let me guess.
They were the four staff members
from Wrath who built this place.
You are correct.
Two males and two females
came to this land.
Each couple raised eight
children each on two farms.
They taught them to read and write, and
how to raise crops and livestock too,
and the moral arguments of good and evil?
which formed the basis of the Taboo Index.
Based on how effectively the first four
were able to pass down these teachings,
it's clear that as humans, they
were incredibly intelligent.
However, there was one among them who was
not only brilliant, but devious as well.
The children this person raised
inherited selfish desires,
such as the hunger to rule and conquer.
However,
the offspring of these children would
eventually become the nobles of this land,
as well as the High Ministers
of the Axiom Church.
One of them, the current
system's supervisor,
is the Pontifex of the Axiom Church,
a woman who controls
everything with an iron fist.
She calls herself Administrator,
the most arrogant name imaginable.
That name…
I heard that Eldrie guy say it.
That's right.
He said he was, like, summoned by this
Pontifex Administrator or something.
Yes, she's the one I've
been talking about.
Sadly,
this Administrator, while
I don't like to admit it,
is my elder twin sister, so to speak.
She is?
How do you mean?
I'm getting to that.
Several decades after the
first four logged out,
the first political marriage was arranged
between two families of the Lord Class.
From that union, a baby girl was born.
Her name was Queen Nella.
Queen Nella, my dear!
Henceforth, your calling is
to research the sacred arts.
Nothing would make me happier, Father!
Thank you.
System, call.
No one else realizes it.
But each sacred word has its own meaning.
Call means to summon.
Generate means to produce.
Come on, this way!
System call.
Generate thermal element.
Form element. Arrow shape.
Fly straight. Discharge!
Lady Queeniella, please help my
husband walk again. Very well.
System call.
Generate luminous element.
Form element.
Liquid shape.
It's a miracle.
Lady Quinella, you are
the holy child of Stacia.
But her gentle smile was a mask.
Quinella had developed a thirst for power,
and now she had the means to seize it.
Very soon, we will have a place
where we can worship the gods.
In order to control
the growing population,
I must put some laws into place to ensure
no one else exceeds my authority level.
I will make hunting taboo.
I will outlaw murder as well.
Lady Quinella, you wish to see me?
This is a holy book containing the
complete words of the goddess Stacia.
It is called the Taboo Index.
Make copies, distribute it to every town
and village, and have the people obey it.
Yes, my lady.
Oh my god.
System call.
Open list.
List, system, call, read, list.
System, call, inspect, list.
Finally, Quinella opened it.
The Forbidden Door.
It was quite the coincidence.
Although I suspect someone from
the outside world helped her.
Let me show you.
System call.
Inspect entire command list.
You're kidding.
What you see before you is the full catalog
of all the Underworld system commands.
Quinella's first order of business was to
restore her life and
halt the aging process.
Then, she restored her beauty.
In an instant, she regained the
dazzling allure of her late teens.
That should have been
enough to satisfy her.
But no.
For Quinella, there could
be no one equal to her.
Even the Cardinal System was
something she deemed a threat.
So she devised a way to
seize the Cardinal System's
authority level using a sacred
art command she composed.
As a result,
she burned the Prime Directive
of the Cardinal System
into her flux light as her
own behavioral principle.
That way, it could not be overwritten.
She just wanted its authority level.
Instead, she ended up fusing her
soul with the Cardinal System.
To uphold order.
That is the prime directive of the Cardinal
System and its reason for existing.
As someone who spent time in a
world controlled by the same system,
you should understand.
Cardinal observes the
actions of players like you,
and it corrects anything that
disrupts the balance of the world.
Without any mercy.
Queen Ella had fainted and was
unconscious for an entire day.
When she woke up, she had ceased
being human in any sense of the word.
She no longer aged or required sustenance.
Her only desire was to preserve this
realm in its current state forever.
I am both ruler and supervisor.
And now, the Pontifex of
the Axiom Church as well.
I am administrator.
If you see the light of the sun,
I will bloom in the night.
I'd be hiding the hurt that hurt.
I'd be able to heal a little bit.
Realist to you!